Art Buchwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Administrative File, 1953-2006 (Box 140-176)
  - Publicity
    - Interview video files
      - The New York Times, "The Last Word," 2007, mss86197_178_220
      - The PBS NewsHour with Jim Lehrer, 2006 Mar. 28
        - Broadcasts, mss86197_178_023; mss86197_178_024
        - Raw video files, mss86197_178_021; mss86197_178_022
      - This Week, 2006 Mar. 12, mss86197_178_019
      - Today Show, 2006, mss86197_178_008
    - Interviews, 1969-2006, undated, (5 folders) (Box 168)
    - Lecture tour, 1962 (Box 168)
    - Magazine covers, 1954-2003 See also Container OV 7, The Newsday Magazine, (3 folders) (Box 168)
    - Photographs, circa 1980-circa 2000, (2 folders) (Box 168)
    - Posters and advertisements (Box 168)
      - Books, circa 1950-circa 1994 See Containers OV 10 and 17, Promotional posters (Box 168)
      - Columns, 1955-1988 See Containers OV 11 and 18, Promotional posters and advertisements (Box 168)
    - Student papers about Buchwald, 1964-1988 (Box 168)
    - Television appearances (Box 168)
      - 1965-1969, (1 folder) (Box 168)
      - 1970-1999, (4 folders) (Box 169)
  - Publishing (Box 169)
    - Article requests, 1983-1988 (Box 169)
    - Copyright (Box 169)
      - Assignments, 1959-1983, (2 folders) (Box 169)
      - Legislation (Mathias Amendment), 1975-1976 (Box 169)
      - Library of Congress, 1976-1977 (Box 169)
      - Los Angeles Times Syndicate, 1973-1994 (Box 169)
      - Renewals, 1953-1994, (14 folders) (Box 170)
    - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1973-1982 (Box 170)
    - Foreign rights, 1962-1967 (Box 170)
    - Los Angeles Times Syndicate (Box 171)
      - 1969-1987 See also Container OV 11, Poster advertisements, 1987, (10 folders) (Box 171)
      - 1988-2005 See also Container OV 11, Poster advertisements, 1993, (8 folders) (Box 172)
    - Permissions (Box 172)
      - 1955-1972, (1 folder) (Box 172)
      - 1984-2004, (7 folders) (Box 173)
    - Playboy, 1964-1984 (Box 173)
    - Putnam Publishing Group (Box 173)
      - 1972-1989, (1 folder) (Box 173)
      - 1990-2002, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - Roslyn Targ Literary Agency, Inc., 1971-1998, (2 folders) (Box 174)
    - Russell and Volkening, Inc., 2003 (Box 174)
    - Royalties (Box 174)
      - ... And Then I Told the President, 1972-1975 (Box 174)
      - The Bollo Caper, 1972-1994 (Box 174)
      - The Buchwald Stops Here, 1978-1993 (Box 174)
      - Down the Seine and Up the Potomac with Art Buchwald, 1978-1982 (Box 174)
      - General (Box 174)
        - 1961-1998, (5 folders) (Box 174)
        - 2000-2005, (1 folder) (Box 175)
      - Getting High in Government Circles, 1980 (Box 175)
      - I Am Not a Crook, 1977-1989 (Box 175)
      - I Never Danced at the White House, 1974-1983 (Box 175)
      - Irving's Delight: At Last! A Cat Story for the Whole Family!, 1975-1980 (Box 175)
      - Laid Back in Washington, 1982-1991 (Box 175)
      - Oh, To Be a Swinger, 1973-1982 (Box 175)
      - Son of the Great Society, 1972-1975 (Box 175)
      - Stella in Heaven: Almost a Novel, 2000-2002 (Box 175)
      - Washington is Leaking, 1977 (Box 175)
      - While Reagan Slept, 1984-1985 (Box 175)
    - Sterling Lord Literistic, Inc., 1983-1989 (Box 175)
    - Syndication, 1981-1997, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Tribune Media Services, 2000-2005, (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Washington Post (Box 175)
      - 1966-1989, (3 folders) (Box 175)
      - 1990-1991, 2005, (1 folder) (Box 176)
  - Speakers bureaus (Box 176)
    - Leigh Bureau / W. Colston Leigh, Inc., 1969-1980 (Box 176)
    - Washington Speakers Bureau, Inc., 1986-2003, (6 folders) (Box 176)
  - Writers Guild of America, 1984-2006, (2 folders) (Box 176)
- Speeches, 1959-2006 (Box 177-192)
  The Speeches series documents events and engagements for which Buchwald served as a speaker or master of ceremonies, was honored, or attended and includes remarks and scheduling information related to his many appearances at events, conferences, conventions, organizational meetings, charity benefits, award banquets, and commencements. A number of Buchwald’s speeches were given at professional organization meetings or for organizations that played important roles in his life such as the Hebrew Orphan Asylum of New York and the New York Herald Tribune. Some of Buchwald’s remarks were given in recognition of awards he received and include honorary degrees, the National Press Club's Fourth Estate Award, and the Horatio Alger Award. Tributes or remembrances given by Buchwald in honor of friends or family members are also documented. Of note is a script Buchwald revised for a production in partnership with the Boston Pops Orchestra of Saint-Saens’ Carnival of the Animals, which includes numerous scripts, correspondence, and press clippings related to the program. Major themes and topics in the speeches include childhood and leaving home, Buchwald’s service in the United States Marine Corps, his years spent in Paris, France, politics and life in Washington, D.C., and depression and mental health.
  Material types include speeches, in both complete and fragmented form, speech cards, notes and transcripts, programs and invitations, correspondence, clippings, photographs, and negatives.
  Arranged alphabetically by grouping.
  - Alphabetical (Box 177)
    - Name (Box 177)
      - Attwood, William, 1993 (Box 177)
      - Botwinick, Edward, 1985 (Box 177)
      - Bradlee, Benjamin C., 1975-2000, (4 folders) (Box 177)
      - Bradlee, Quinn, undated (Box 177)
      - Brokaw, Meredith, 1993 (Box 177)
      - Brokaw, Tom, 1984-1990, 2002 (Box 177)
      - Brown, Don, 1999 (Box 177)
      - Buchwald, Ann, 1994 (Box 177)
      - Buchwald, Art, 2005 (Box 177)
      - Buchwald, Joseph, 1972 (Box 177)
      - Brustein, Robert, 1996 (Box 177)
      - Byrne, John J., 1984 (Box 177)
      - Califano, Hilary, 1989 (Box 177)
      - Califano, Joseph A., Jr., 1978-1979, 1991-1993 (Box 177)
      - Chandler, Otis, 1985 (Box 177)
      - Cobey, Ellie, 1976 (Box 177)
      - Conrad, Paul, 1986 (Box 177)
      - Cook, Don, 1995 (Box 177)
      - Cronkite, Walter, 1978-1982 (Box 177)
      - Cuomo, Mario, 1983, 1995 (Box 177)
      - Dalinsky, Harry, 1981-1992, (2 folders) (Box 177)
      - Davidson, Ralph, 1992 (Box 177)
      - Davis, Marty, 1989 (Box 177)
      - Davis, Marvin, 1984 (Box 178)
      - Diana, Princess of Wales, and Colin L. Powell, 1995 (Box 178)
      - Dreyfuss, Richard, 1991 (Box 178)
      - Durr, Clifford J., 1994 (Box 178)
      - Durr, Virginia Foster, 1983-1999 (Box 178)
      - Evans, Rowly, 1993 (Box 178)
      - Finley, Larry, 1998 (Box 178)
      - Ford, Gerald R., 1978, 1986, 1994 (Box 178)
      - Geyelin, Philip L., 2003 (Box 178)
      - Goldmark, Peter C., undated (Box 178)
      - Gordon, Jack, 1991 (Box 178)
      - Gordon, Milton, 1990 (Box 178)
      - Graham, Katharine, 1987-1993 (Box 178)
      - Grann, Phyllis, 2002 (Box 178)
      - Grinberg, Gedalio ("Gerry"), 1981 (Box 178)
      - Guggenheim, Charles, 1990 (Box 178)
      - Hackney, Lucy, 1988, 1997 (Box 178)
      - Hackney, Sheldon, 1991 (Box 178)
      - Harriman, W. Averell, 1969 (Box 178)
      - Harris, Ira, undated (Box 178)
      - Hawke, Jerry, 1993 (Box 178)
      - Healy, Robert, 1989 (Box 178)
      - Hope, Bob, 1986 July (Box 178)
      - Kennedy, Edward M. (Edward Moore), 1967 (Box 178)
      - Kennedy, Ethel, 1978, 1988-1993 (Box 178)
      - Kennedy, Michael, and Vicki Gifford, 1981 (Box 178)
      - King, Larry, 1993 (Box 178)
      - Lindsay, John, 1966-1967 (Box 178)
      - Marcus, Stanley, 1982 (Box 178)
      - Michener, James, 1975 (Box 178)
      - Moyers, Bill D., 1966-1967 (Box 178)
      - Nelson, Jack, 1996 (Box 178)
      - Novak, Robert, 1989 (Box 178)
      - O'Donnell, Pierce, 1989-1990 (Box 178)
      - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, 1978 (Box 178)
      - Parnis, Molly, 1990 (Box 178)
      - Plimpton, George, 2003 (Box 178)
      - Richardson, Elliot L., 1984 (Box 178)
      - Rogers, Henry, 1991 (Box 178)
      - Rubin, Miles, and Nancy Rubin, 1991 (Box 178)
      - Ruhe, Jeff, 1988 (Box 178)
      - Ruhe, Jeff, and Courtney Kennedy, 1981 (Box 178)
      - Salomon, Bill, 1978 (Box 178)
      - Scharffenberger, George, 1989 (Box 178)
      - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr., 1964, 1981, 1997 (Box 179)
      - Schwarzenegger, Arnold, and Maria Shriver, 1986 (Box 179)
      - Shipman, Robert, undated (Box 179)
      - Shore, Dinah, 1994 (Box 179)
      - Shriver, Sargent, 1968, 1977-1978, 1990 (Box 179)
      - Shriver, Timothy, and Linda Potter, 1986 (Box 179)
      - Shriver and Kennedy family, undated (Box 179)
      - Siegel, Herbert, 2003 (Box 179)
      - Simon, Bob, 1985 (Box 179)
      - Smith, Stan, 1996 (Box 179)
      - Steele, Richard, 1981 (Box 179)
      - Steinbrenner, George, 1979 (Box 179)
      - Stern, Phil, 1986 (Box 179)
      - Stevens, George, 1980, 1992 (Box 179)
      - Stevenson, Adlai, 1965-1966 (Box 179)
      - Stone, Peter, 2003 (Box 179)
      - Styron, William, 1987, 1993-1995, 2006 (Box 179)
      - Seuss, Dr., 1984 (Box 179)
      - Torem, Charles, 1993 (Box 179)
      - Valenti, Jack, 1981-1986, 1992 (Box 179)
      - Wallace, Mike, 1988-1993, 1999, 2005 (Box 179)
      - Williams, Edward Bennett, 1977-1980 (Box 179)
      - Wolper, David L., 1977-1984, 1990-1993 (Box 179)
      - Wolper, Gloria, 1990-1993 (Box 179)
    - Subject (Box 179)
      - Lists of speeches by subject, 1975-1990 (Box 179)
      - Actuaries, 1998 (Box 179)
      - Advertising, 1985, 1992 (Box 179)
      - A&E Biography, 1998 Feb. 10 (Box 179)
      - Aeronautics, aviation, 1983-1989 (Box 179)
      - Amnesty International, 1975-1978 (Box 179)
      - Anti-Defamation League, 1980-1982, 1989, 1997 (Box 179)
      - Arts, 1981-1987 (Box 179)
      - Automobiles, 1985-1989 (Box 179)
      - Banking, 1980-2003, (2 folders) (Box 180)
      - Canada, 1983, 1990 (Box 180)
      - Carnival of the Animals, 1971-1991, undated, (2 folders) (Box 180)
      - Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse (CASA), 1993-2002 (Box 180)
      - CBS 60 Minutes, 1988 (Box 180)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1990-1992 (Box 180)
      - Charities, 1976-1993, (2 folders) (Box 180)
      - Chemical, pharmaceutical, 1979-1990 (Box 180)
      - Children, 1981, 1988-1989 (Box 181)
      - Commencements, 1964-2004, (6 folders) (Box 181)
      - Computers, 1980-1992 (Box 181)
      - Education, 1985-1993 (Box 182)
      - Ellis Island, undated (Box 182)
      - Financial institutions, 1979-1989 (Box 182)
      - Golf, undated (Box 182)
      - Gridiron Club, 1964-1991, (4 folders) (Box 182)
      - Hebrew Orphan Asylum of New York, 1983, 1990-2001 (Box 182)
      - High school graduations, 1975, 1983, 1996 (Box 183)
      - Horatio Alger Award, 1989 (Box 183)
      - Humor, 1984-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 183)
      - HUMOR Project, 1999-2000 (Box 183)
      - Insurance, 1981-1983, 1988, 1992 (Box 183)
      - Introductions, 1973-2003, undated, (10 folders) (Box 183)
      - Jewish Child Care Association, 1972-1974, 1989 (Box 184)
      - Jewish groups, 1972, 1983, 1989-1998 (Box 184)
      - Jewish men, undated (Box 184)
      - Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, Md., 1988-1989 (Box 184)
      - Juvenile Diabetes Promise Ball, 1976-1977 (Box 184)
      - Law and lawyers, 1975-1997, (3 folders) (Box 184)
      - Leaving Home speech, undated (Box 184)
      - Libraries, 1972, 1980-1992, 1997-2005 (Box 184)
      - Medical (Box 184)
        - 1965, 1974-1986, (1 folder) (Box 184)
        - 1987-2001, undated, (3 folders) (Box 185)
      - Mental health, 1986-2005, undated, (3 folders) (Box 185)
      - Miscellaneous speeches, undated, (1 folder) (Box 185)
      - Miscellaneous speeches, undated, (1 folder) (Box 186)
      - Movie industry, 1990, undated (Box 186)
      - Multiple Sclerosis Dinner for Pete Rozelle, 1976 (Box 186)
      - National Kidney Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box 186)
      - National Press Club, 1986, 2004 (Box 186)
      - Naturalization, 1986-1990 (Box 186)
      - Newspapers, 1976-1997, (2 folders) (Box 186)
      - New York Herald Tribune, 1983-1988 (Box 186)
      - New York, N.Y., 1983-1989, 1995 (Box 186)
      - North American Watch, 1980-1984 (Box 186)
      - Oil, 1980, 1986-1988, 1997 (Box 186)
      - Palm Beach, Fla., 1991 (Box 186)
      - Paramount Pictures Corp., 1990-1992, 1998 (Box 186)
      - Paris, France, 1986-1987, 1992-1996 (Box 187)
      - Philadelphia, Pa., 1987 (Box 187)
      - Planned Parenthood, 1981-1986 (Box 187)
      - Politics, undated (Box 187)
      - Possible Dreams Auction, undated (Box 187)
      - Publishing, 1978-1981, 1987-1996 (Box 187)
      - Reading for the Blind, 2001 (Box 187)
      - Real estate, 1988-1992 (Box 187)
      - Red Smith Lecture in Journalism, 1982-1988 (Box 187)
      - Renaissance weekend, 2004-2005 (Box 187)
      - Retail and trade, 1978-1997 (Box 187)
      - Salomon Brothers, 1975, 1981-1988 (Box 187)
      - Speech materials and fragments, undated (Box 187)
      - State Department, 1984, 1990 (Box 188)
      - Tapings, 1975-1980, 1998 (Box 188)
      - TED speech, 2002 (Box 188)
      - Telecommunications, 1988 (Box 188)
      - Tennis, 1980-1988 (Box 188)
      - Trade associations, 1988 (Box 188)
      - United States Marine Corps, 1980-2001, (2 folders) (Box 188)
      - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., 1980, 1985-1998 (Box 188)
      - Watergate, undated (Box 188)
      - Wine, 1981 (Box 188)
      - Women, 1972, 1979-1994 (Box 188)
      - Wood's Hole, Mass., undated (Box 188)
      - World Affairs Council, 1989 June 23 (Box 188)
      - Writers, 1981, 1990 (Box 188)
  - Chronological (Box 188)
    - 1959, (1 folder) (Box 188)
    - 1960-1980 See also Container OV 11, Poster; Container OV 10, Dinner napkin, (11 folders) (Box 189)
    - 1980-1989, (10 folders) (Box 190)
    - 1990-1996, (10 folders) (Box 191)
    - 1997-2006, (10 folders) (Box 192)
  - Speech cards, undated See Containers OV 2-OV 4, OV 6, same title (Box 192)
- Personal File, 1885-2007 (Box 192-222)
  The Personal File documents Buchwald’s youth, early career in Paris, France, family, health, and death. The bulk of the material chronicles Buchwald’s childhood in the Hebrew Orphan Asylum’s foster care system, service in the United States Marine Corps, and years at the University of Southern California. Documents and printed ephemera reflecting Buchwald’s fourteen years in Paris (1948-1962) are comprised in this series and document his work as a critic and humorist for the New York Herald Tribune, as well as his household and family life at that time. The Personal File also contains Buchwald’s family papers, which include letters with his sisters, in-laws, and other family members and documents collected and created by Buchwald’s wife, Ann. Ann Buchwald’s papers contain correspondence with Art and other members of her family, as well as transcripts and drafts of her memoir, Seems Like Yesterday. Early examples of Buchwald’s writings are found throughout the Personal File beginning with a poem written when he was twelve years old, circa 1937. Several newsletters for which Buchwald wrote while in the United States Marine Corps, including The Coral Courier and The U-Man Comedy, are also in this series. His academic essays, produced for courses in creative and script writing at the University of Southern California, are well represented, as are pieces written for school publications, The Daily Trojan and WAMPUS. This series also includes early columns Buchwald wrote while in Paris. These consist of articles written in 1948 when he was a stringer for Variety and article drafts for the New York Herald Tribune.
  Material types include address and appointment books, correspondence, digital files, family papers, honorary degrees and awards, oral histories, medical files, military documents, identification cards, marriage documents, photographs, and wills.
  - Address books (Box 192)
    - Association de la Presse Anglo-Américaine de Paris, 1959 (Box 192)
    - Duplicate addresses, circa 2002, (2 folders) (Box 192)
    - European numbers, circa 1962-circa 1992, (2 folders) (Box 192)
    - European numbers, circa 1962-circa 1992, (6 folders) (Box 193)
    - Household numbers, circa 1974-circa 1987, (5 folders) (Box 193)
    - Household numbers, circa 1974-circa 1987, (3 folders) (Box 194)
    - Rolodex, circa 1990-circa 1998, (5 folders) (Box 194)
    - Untitled books (Box 194)
      - Book 1, circa 1964, (2 folders) (Box 194)
      - Book 2, circa 1974-circa 1975, (1 folder) (Box 195)
      - Book 3, circa 1974-circa 1977, (2 folders) (Box 195)
      - Book 4, circa 1977-circa 1982, (6 folders) (Box 195)
      - Book 4, circa 1977-circa 1982, (2 folders) (Box 196)
      - Book 5, circa 1980-circa 1991, (3 folders) (Box 196)
      - Book 6, 1995 (Box 196)
      - Book 7, 1997 (Box 196)
    - Washington numbers, circa 2003, 2005, (2 folders) (Box 196)
  - Appointment and address books (Box 196)
    - 1948-1962, (1 folder) (Box 196)
    - 1948-1972, (4 folders) (Box 197)
    - 1972-1980, (3 folders) (Box 198)
    - 1981-1988, (3 folders) (Box 199)
    - 1991-2004, undated, (4 folders) (Box 200)
    - undated, (3 folders) (Box 201)
  - Artworks and artifacts (Box 201)
    - Billfold, undated (Box 201)
    - "The Buchwald Stops Here" nameplate, undated (Box 201)
    - Miscellany, 1949-2004 See Container OV 17, Photographs (Box 201)
    - Paintings and prints, 1959-1960, undated See Container OV 11, same heading (Box 201)
    - Paul VI, Pope, trip to Israel, 1964 (Box 201)
    - Wallet at time of death, 2007 (Box 202)
  - Awards and honors (Box 202)
    - First Order of the Owl award, PowerPoint presentation, National Press Club, 2004, mss86197_178_229
    - Honorary degrees (Box 202)
      - Brandeis University, Waltham, Mass., 1987 (Box 202)
      - College of the Holy Cross, Worcester, Mass., 1988 (Box 202)
      - College of William and Mary, Williamsburg, Va., 1980 (Box 202)
      - Emerson College, Boston, Mass., 1978 (Box 202)
      - Gallaudet College, Washington, D.C., 1976 (Box 202)
      - Georgetown University, Washington, D.C., 1979 (Box 202)
      - Lakeland College, Sheboygan, Wis., 2000 (Box 202)
      - Miami University, Oxford, Ohio, 1974 (Box 202)
      - Providence College, Providence, R.I., 1970 (Box 202)
      - Roger Williams College, Bristol, R.I., 1971 (Box 202)
      - Roosevelt University, Chicago, Ill., 1981 (Box 202)
      - University of San Diego, San Diego, Calif., 1976 (Box 202)
      - University of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., 1992-1993, (2 folders) (Box 202)
      - Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1975 (Box 202)
      - Washington College, Chestertown, Md., 1985 (Box 203)
      - Washington University, St. Louis, Mo., 1975 (Box 203)
      - Wesleyan University, Middletown, Conn., 1969 (Box 203)
      - Yale University, New Haven, Conn., 1970 (Box 203)
    - Joke awards, 1965-1978, 1987-1992, undated See also Containers OV 7 and OV 17, Certificates (Box 203)
    - Other awards, 1958-2006, undated, (3 folders) (Box 203)
    - Pulitzer Prize (Box 203)
      - 75th anniversary, 1991 (Box 203)
      - Correspondence, 1982, (5 folders) (Box 203)
      - Entry, 1981, 1989, (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - Press and clippings, 1982 (Box 204)
  - Business cards, undated (Box 204)
  - Childhood (Box 204)
    - Birth certificate receipt, 1948 (Box 204)
    - Correspondence, 1982-2003, undated, (2 folders) (Box 204)
    - Early writings, circa 1937-1939 (Box 204)
    - Hebrew Orphan Asylum of New York (Box 204)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 204)
      - The Luckiest Orphans: A History of the Hebrew Orphan Asylum of New York by Hyman Bogen, undated (Box 204)
      - Miscellany, 1983-1988, undated (Box 204)
      - Publications and clippings, 1927-1999, undated, (1 folder) (Box 204)
      - Publications and clippings, 1927-1999, undated, (1 folder) (Box 205)
      - Screenplay, "A Home on the Hill," by John C. Scott, undated (Box 205)
      - Seligman Solomon Society, 1925 (Box 205)
    - Newspapers from day of birth, 1925 See also Container OV 11, same heading (Box 205)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 205)
    - Public School 35 Elementary School, Hollis, N.Y., 1936-1941 (Box 205)
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 205)
    - Social worker case history, 1931-1941 (Box 205)
  - Collected historical documents (Box 205)
    - Farrar, F. W. (Frederic William), "The Modern Preacher," undated (Box 205)
    - New York Tribune letter, 1885 (Box 205)
    - Roll call on impeachment, U.S. House of Representatives, 1974 (Box 205)
  - Death and estate (Box 205)
    - Letters of condolence, 2007, (2 folders) (Box 205)
    - Letters of condolence, 2007, (3 folders) (Box 206)
    - Memorial service (Box 206)
      - Planning files, 2007 (Box 206)
      - Scrapbooks, 2007 See Containers OV 14-16, same title (Box 206)
        - Photographs and PowerPoint slide show, circa 2007, mss86197_178_202
        - Digital files used to compile the scrapbooks, 2007, Contains photographs, correspondence, columns, articles, audio files, notes, lists, and copies of the Federal Bureau of Investigation's file on Buchwald in the 1950s and 1960s, among other documents and files.; mss86197_178_203
    - Obituaries, 2007 (Box 206)
    - "Too Soon to Say Goodbye," audio recording of song by Carly Simon, 2006, mss86197_178_010
    - Wills and trusts (Box 206)
      - 1960-1991, (4 folders) (Box 206)
      - 1995-2001, undated, (1 folder) (Box 207)
  - Electric typewriter, 1972-1973 (Box 207)
  - Family papers (Box 207)
    - Buchwald, Ann (Box 207)
      - Address books, undated (Box 207)
      - Adoption paperwork, undated (Box 207)
      - Correspondence (Box 207)
        - Buchwald, Art, 1949-1990, undated, (9 folders) (Box 207)
        - Buchwald, Joel, 1962, undated (Box 208)
        - Family, 1949-1993, (5 folders) (Box 208)
        - General, 1950-1997, undated (Box 208)
      - Death (Box 208)
        - Letters of condolence, 1994, (2 folders) (Box 208)
        - Memorial service, 1994 (Box 208)
      - Diary, 1954-1958 (Box 208)
      - Immunization cards, 1958-1974 (Box 208)
      - Miscellany, 1953-1962, 1980-1992, undated (Box 208)
      - Professional file, 1949-1953, 1965, 1980, undated (Box 208)
      - Seems Like Yesterday (Box 209)
        - Copy-edited manuscript, 1980, (3 folders) (Box 209)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 209)
        - Early drafts, circa 1977-1979, (4 folders) (Box 209)
        - Early drafts, circa 1977-1979, (8 folders) (Box 210)
        - Galley proof, 1980 (Box 211)
        - Late drafts, circa 1980, (5 folders) (Box 211)
        - Oral history interview, undated, (3 folders) (Box 211)
        - Publicity, 1979-1981 See also Container OV 11, Promotional poster (Box 211)
        - Reviews, 1980 (Box 211)
    - Buchwald, Joseph, 1971-1972, undated (Box 211)
    - Buchwald, Oscar (Box 212)
      - Ellis Island, 1982-1989, undated (Box 212)
      - Reminiscences, undated (Box 212)
    - Correspondence (Box 212)
      - 1994, (8 folders) (Box 212)
      - 1995-2006, undated, (3 folders) (Box 213)
    - Genealogy, 2002, undated (Box 213)
    - Gordon, Alice, 2005 (Box 213)
    - Home videos, 1958-1968, 1974, Footage includes Buchwald family in Paris, Martha's Vineyard, Mass., Pet Show, 1964 New York World's Fair, Lyndon Baines Johnson in the Oval Office of the White House, Buchwald Easter parties, 1966-1968, among other events and occasions.; mss86197_178_155; mss86197_178_156; mss86197_178_157; mss86197_178_158
    - Marriage (Box 213)
      - Documents, 1952 (Box 213)
      - Wedding anniversaries, 1977-1983, undated See also Container OV 7, Card (Box 213)
  - Forest Hills High School, Queens, N.Y. (Box 213)
    - Alumnus of the Year award, 1966 (Box 213)
    - Diploma, 1945-1946, 1975 (Box 213)
    - Pass to leave building, 1942 (Box 213)